Bob Bullock Campaigns papers, Inclusive: 1970-1996, Bulk: 1973-1996
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
Bob Bullock Campaigns papers
Inclusive: 1970-1996, Bulk: 1973-1996
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials http://www.baylor.edu/lib/bcpm/
5A
Bullock, Robert "Bob" Douglas, Sr., 1929 - 1999
49 document boxes
The Bob Bullock Campaigns collection spans the campaigns of Bob Bullock from 1974 through post-1995. The collection contains campaign materials, including correspondence, invitations, endorsements, publications, itineraries, polls, financial material, and additional materials.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Good.
Biography/Profile
Bullock maintained a full-time campaign office at various Austin locations for almost 20 years. State campaign laws and his experiences early in his term as Comptroller taught him the wisdom of keeping political and state officeholder operations separate.
A small campaign staff ran a mail, scheduling, fundraising, and administrative office year round. During election years, the staff was reinforced with enough paid workers and volunteers to run the effective political campaigns that made Bullock’s reputation as a formidable opponent. In addition, there was usually a network of hundreds of volunteers in counties all over the state coordinating campaign stops, fundraisers, and press conferences.
While he was Comptroller and Lt. Governor, Bullock hosted an annual fundraising reception, first class in promotion and execution, for as many as a thousand supporters and friends. In addition to the invitations to these receptions, the collection contains the one-of-a-kind souvenirs or mementos that were given to every guest and became a hallmark of the Bullock fundraisers. These items include personalized pens, lapel pins, paperweights, gavels, neck scarves, and even a Bullock drawing commissioned from Pulitzer Prize-winning cartoonist Ben Sargent.
Scope and Content
Bob Bullock Campaigns collection is divided into seven series: 1974 Campaign, 1978 Campaign, 1982 Campaign, 1986 Campaign, 1990 Campaign, 1994 Campaign, and Post-January 1995, encompassing the six campaigns in which Bob Bullock ran for public office. The materials found in Bullock’s Campaign collection consist of campaign files, correspondence, election results and related materials, endorsements, including questionnaires and notebooks, financial materials, invitations, and issue files. Also found in the collection are itineraries and invitation declines, campaign memorabilia, a section on Bullock's political opponents, campaign notebooks, poll information, position papers, and publicity in the form of articles, brochures, news clippings, newsletters, press releases, assorted publications, and reports.
The strength of the Campaign collection lies in the 1990 Campaign series and the progression of campaign materials throughout the series. As the largest series and the first campaign for Lieutenant Governor, the 1990 Campaign shows the development, detail, and implementation of a winning political campaign. The attention to detail in researching issues and in preparation for opponents reflects Bullock’s drive and intensity. The embracing of different campaign techniques throughout the six campaigns shows the growth and use of new mediums to reach constituents and influence votes.
Arrangement
The Bob Bullock Campaigns collection is organized by campaign years and separated into seven series: I. 1974 Campaign, II. 1978 Campaign, III. 1982 Campaign, IV. 1986 Campaign, V. 1990 Campaign, VI. 1994 Campaign, and VII. Post-January 1995. Within these series are many subseries, and within subseries in V. 1990 Campaign and VI. 1994 Campaign, are also sub-subseries.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to the W. R. Poage Legislative Library in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. 5A. Acquired 1998-03-15
Related Resources
Items in related collections
Bob Bullock Lieutenant Governor papers, Inclusive: 1991-1999, Bulk: 1991-1999
Bob Bullock Comptroller of Public Accounts papers, Inclusive: 1970-1991, Bulk: 1975-1990
Bob Bullock Media
Bob Bullock Personal
Related references
Bob Bullock Campaigns collection, Accession #5A, Box #, Folder #, The Baylor Collections of Political Materials, W. R. Poage Legislative Library, Baylor University.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
Bullock, Bob -- Archives.; Bullock, Bob -- Political activity.
Subjects (Organizations)
Texas. Comptroller's Office.; Texas. Office of the Lieutenant Governor.
Subjects
Lieutenant governors -- Texas.; Newsletters.; Political campaigns -- Texas.; Political candidates -- Texas.; Politicians -- Texas.; Press releases.
Genres
Brochures.; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.); Correspondence.; Invitation cards.; Records (Documents); Souvenirs (Keepsakes)
- 1974 Campaign, 1970-1980; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Good.
  Biography/Profile
  In 1974, Bullock campaigned for Texas Comptroller of Public Accounts and was elected. The 1974 Campaign series contains eleven subseries: General, Flyers, Radio, Correspondence, Endorsements — Newspapers, Endorsements — Tom Green County, Financial, Invitations — Fundraisers, Itineraries, Position Papers, and Publications.
  The General subseries has a publicity packet, biographical sketches, bumper stickers, and other general campaign materials. Flyers and Radio contributed to publicity surrounding Bullock’s 1974 campaign. The Correspondence subseries contains campaign correspondence from individuals, other politicians, or campaign staff members. The two Endorsements subseries contain candidate endorsements found in newspaper clippings and correspondence pertaining to Tom Green County. Financial contains contribution and expense reports. Invitations reflect fundraising and campaign events for Bullock and other politicians. They include actual invitations and pledge cards. The Itineraries subseries shows Bullock’s dedication to campaign travel, and holds schedules, trip folders, general travel materials, and news clippings. Position papers detail Bullock’s position on critical issues such as crime, drugs, and higher education. Some are in the form of reports while others are found in correspondence and memos. The Publications subseries covers various forms of public media which Bullock collected or people sent him about himself, his campaigns, and politics in general. It contains articles, news clippings, newsletters, and press releases, arranged chronologically and pertaining to information about the political climate and events surrounding Bullock’s political campaigns.
  - General, undated; 1
    - Publicity Packet, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Biographical Sketch, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Biographical Sketch, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Biographical Sketch, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Biographical Sketch, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bumper Stickers, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Card File-Waco, A-L, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Card File-Waco, M-Z, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Flyers, circa 1973-1974; 2
    - “Bob Bullock: The Issues and the Answers”, circa 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - “Bob Bullock: The Job and The Man”, circa 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - “Bob Bullock: You Know Where He Is”, circa 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - “Help Bob Bullock Fight The Tax Rip-Off”, circa 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - “The Man, The Office, The Choice, The Job”, circa 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - “Time to Bring the Comptroller’s Office Out of the Dark Ages”, circa 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Radio, 1974; 3
    - Radio Spot-Audio Tape, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Returned Support Cards, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1973; 4
    - Cervelli, A. Fred, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Endorsements - Newspapers, 1974-1977; 5
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1974 April (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1974 May (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Newspapers-Correspondence, 1974 September (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Newspapers-Correspondence, 1974 October (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Newspapers-Correspondence, 1974 November (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Newspaper List, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Newspaper List, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Endorsements - Tom Green County, 1973-1974; 6
    - Correspondence, 1973 March (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1973 May (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1973 June (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1973 August (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1973 September (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1973 October (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1974 March (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1974 May (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1974 July (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1974 August (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1974 October (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1974 November (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, circa 1974 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Financial, 1973-1976; 7
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report (1 of 2), 1973 January 29-1974 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report (2 of 2), 1973 January 29-1974 March 25 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report, 1974 Jan 1-April 1 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report, 1974 March 26-April 24 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report, 1974 April 25-May 18 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report, 1974 May 19-June 18 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report, 1974 June 19-September 26 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report, 1974 September 27-October 26 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report, 1974 October 27-November 19 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report, 1974 November 20-December 31 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Contribution Acknowledgements, 1974 May (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Contribution Request: Carr, Waggoner, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Contribution Request: Denton, Lane, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Contribution Request: McAlmon, George, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Contribution Request: National Committee for an Effective Congress, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Contribution Request: Pickle, J. J. (Jake), undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Contribution Requests: Smith, Preston, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Contribution Request: Wayne, John, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Contribution Request: Yarborough, Ralph, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Invitations - Fundraisers, 1970-1974; 8
    - “Meet Bob Bullock”, 1974 April 24 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Bentsen, Lloyd, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Bentsen, Lloyd, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Cobb, Dean, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Gill, Hubert, circa 1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Sartain, John, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Itineraries, 1973-1974; 9
    - General, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Trip-San Marcos, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Trip-Haskell, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - General, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Campaign Tours Through September 28, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - News Clippings, 1973 July-September (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Schedule Confirmations, 1974 April (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Schedule Confirmations, 1974 October (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Position Papers, 1973-1974; 10
    - “Bob Bullock-The Issues and The Answers”, circa 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - “Bob Bullock-The Job and The Man”, circa 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - “The Office of Comptroller, Although Presently Occupied, Is not Filled”, circa 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Publications, 1972-1980; 11
    - Articles, 1972 March (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - News Clippings, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - News Clippings, Editorial List, 1974 November 3-1980 February 11 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Newsletters, circa 1974 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Press Releases, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Press Releases, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- 1978 Campaign, 1975-1986; 2
  Bullock successfully campaigned for Comptroller a second time in 1978. The 1978 Campaign series contains six subseries: General, Endorsements, Financial, Invitations — Fundraisers, Polls, and Publications.
  The General subseries contains materials used in political campaigns, such as publicity packets, biographical sketches, brochures, envelopes, and letterhead. The Endorsements subseries includes procedures, while the Financial subseries holds contributions and expense reports, and correspondence. The Invitations subseries reflects fundraising and campaign events for Bullock and other politicians, including actual invitations and pledge cards. Correspondence regarding different events and occasions Bullock was invited to are located in this section. Polls contains a telephone survey, and Publications holds public media that Bullock collected or people sent him about himself, his campaigns, and politics in general. This involves news clippings and press releases in this series.
  - General, 1976-1978; 1
    - 1978 Campaign Publicity Packet (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Biographical Sketch, 1976 March 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Biographical Sketch, circa 1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Biographical Sketch, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Brochure, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Comptroller’s Innovations of Interest to Businessman, 1977 September 8 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Comptroller-Recent Major New Programs, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Envelopes and Letterhead, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Statement of Bob Bullock, Comptroller of Public Accounts, circa 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Endorsements, 1986; 2
    - Procedures, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Financial, 1975-1978; 3
    - Campaign Contribution and Expenditure Report, 1975 January-December (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expenditure Report, 1976 January 1-July 12 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expenditure Report, 1977 January-December (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expenditure Report, 1978 January-December (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expenditure Report, 1977 September 27-1978 April 5 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Invitations - Fundraisers, 1976-1978; 4
    - Bentsen, Lloyd, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Briscoe, Dolph, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Daniel, Price Jr., 1978 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Earle, Ronald, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Price, Ray, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Strauss, Robert S. (Bob), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Robert S. (Bob), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee Dinner, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Senate District Six Democrats Breakfast, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Polls, 1976; 5
    - Texas AFL-CIO Right to Contract Poll-Phone Survey, 1976 February-May (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Publications, 1974-1980; 6
    - News Clippings: Editorial List, 1974 November 3-1980 February 11 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Press Releases, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- 1982 Campaign, 1974-1986; 3
  For a third time, Bullock campaigned for Comptroller and won. The 1982 Campaign series contains nine subseries: General, Endorsements — Groups, Endorsements — Newspapers, Financial, Invitations, Itineraries, Polls, Position Papers, and Publications.
  The General subseries contains materials used in political campaigns, such as press packets, flyers, brochures, bumper stickers, buttons, apparel, envelopes, and letterhead, in addition to other general campaign files. The Endorsements subseries are split into Groups and Newspapers, containing numerous candidate endorsements made by Bullock; correspondence and endorsements of Bob Bullock by groups and organizations; and clippings of endorsements by newspapers. Financial contains contribution and expense reports, and contributor lists. Invitations reflect fundraising and campaign events for Bullock and other politicians, including invitations and pledge cards. The Itineraries subseries holds trip folders to various locations included in his campaign travel schedule. Polls contains information on election surveys, public attitude surveys, and analyses of polling information. The Position Papers subseries includes a statement of Bullock’s positions on critical issues. Publications within this series includes news clippings and press releases.
  - General, 1975-1986; 1
    - Biographical Sketch, circa 1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Biographical Sketch, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Brochure, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Bumper Stickers, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Button: “Bullock-Comptroller/82”, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Hat: “Bullock-Comptroller/82”, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - T-shirt: “Bullock Comptroller/82”, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Envelopes-Large, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Envelopes and Letterhead, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Records, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Status Report, 1979 July 27 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Executive Summary, 1975-1981 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Field Offices and Managers-Enforcement, 1982 March (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Flyer-“Bob Bullock-Comptroller of Public Accounts”, circa 1982 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Flyer-“Bob Bullock Makes Money for Texas”, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Flyer-“Resume/Statistics”, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Highlights of the Comptroller’s Department, 1975-1981 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - House of Representatives & Senate Member List, 67th Legislature, 1981 January (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - “Based on Exhaustive Studies” Ad Layout, circa 1986 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - “Of These Are Legends MadeEL”, 1981 July 10 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Turnover Analysis for Selected State Agencies, 1981 September 1-1982 February 28 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Staff, 1982 March (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Endorsements — Groups, 1982; 2
    - Correspondence, 1982 January (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1982 March (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1982 April (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1982 May (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1982 September (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1982 October 6-25 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1982 October 26-29 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - American Federation of Teachers, Texas United Faculty, 1982 April (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Austin Lesbian/Gay Political Caucus, 1982 October (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Austin Progressive Coalition, 1982 April (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Baptist Ministers Association of Houston and Vicinity, 1982 April, October (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Bexar County Women’s Political Caucus, 1982 April (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Black Organization for Leadership Development, 1982 April, October (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Black Voters Action Project, 1982 May (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Brazos Coalition of Black Democrats, 1982 April (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Brownbuilders Political Action Committee-Brown & Root, Inc., 1982 April (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Citizens United for Rehabilitation of Errants, 1982 October (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Corpus Christi Coalition of Black Democrats, 1982 April (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Coalition of Black Democrats, 1982 February (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Dallas Gay Political Caucus, 1982 April, October (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Democratic Progressive Voters League, 1982 April (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - East Texas Chapter Texas State Employees Union, AFL-CIO, 1982 August (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Galveston County Democrats, 1982 April (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Gay Political Caucus, 1982 September (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Harris County Council of Organizations, 1982 October (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Harris County Democrats, 1982 April (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Harris County Hispanic Caucus, 1982 April, October (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Harris County Sheriff’s Deputies Association, 1982 May (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Houston Automobile Dealers Association, 1982 May, October (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Houston Fireman’s Relief and Retirement Fund, 1990 March (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Houston Professional Firefighter’s Association, Local #341, 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Ironworker’s Political Action Committee, Ironworker’s Local #66, 1982 March (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Lesbian & Gay Democrats of Texas, 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - List of Group Endorsements for 1982, 1989 August 12 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Mexican American Democrats of Travis County, 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - North Austin Democrats, 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Oak Lawn Democrats, 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Organization-Association List, Primary, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Senior Citizens Council of Bexar County, 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - South Austin Democrats, 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Texas AFL-CIO, 1982 October (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Texas Agriculture Political Action Committee, 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Texas Coalition of Black Democrats, 1982 February (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Texas Consumer Association, 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Texas Democrats, 1982 February (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Texas Federation of Teachers, AFT, AFL-CIO, 1982 March (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Texas Legislative Board, United Transportation Union, 1982 April, October (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Texas State Association of Fire Fighters, 1982 August (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Texas State Teachers Association, 1982 July (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Texas United Bingo Political Action Committee, 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Texas Women’s Political Caucus, 1982 March-April (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Travis County Democratic Women’s Committees, 1982 May (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - United Auto Workers, 1982 March (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - University Young Democrats, 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Endorsements — Newspapers, 1982-1986; 3
    - Procedures, circa 1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Newspapers, 1982 February (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Newspapers, 1982 March (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Newspapers (1 of 2), 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Newspapers (2 of 2), 1982 April (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Newspapers, 1982 May (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Newspapers, 1982 June (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Newspapers, 1982 September (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Newspapers, 1982 October (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Editorial List-General Election, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Editorials-Primary Election, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - List-Democratic Primary, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - List With Addresses-Primary, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Publication/Organization List, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Summaries, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Financial, 1979-1985; 4
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report, 1979 January 1-April 30 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report, 1980 January 1-December 31 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report (1 of 2), 1981 January 1-December 31 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report (2 of 2), 1981 January 1-December 31 (Box 6, Folder 7)